The World Will Quake In Fear
Arachnoquake is a horror, science fiction film directed by Griff Furst.
Giant albino spiders break free from the depths of Earth in New
Orleans, making everyone’s worst nightmare a reality.
Charlie, played by Edward Furlong.
Paul, played by Bug Hall.
Petra, played by Olivia Hardt.
Major Crandle, played by Gralen Bryant Banks.
Katelynn, played by Tracey Gold.
Tina, played by Tiara Ashleigh.
Arachnoquake is a 2012 made for television horror film directed by Griff Furst
and starring Megan Adelle, Gralen Bryant Banks, and Paul Boocock.
It aired on Syfy.
The film explores themes of panic, spider, giant spider, monster movie.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.